<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>My website</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is a virtual proof that I&apos;m awesome</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Platy Studio- Revolutionizing Video Production with AI</title>
        <description>
          Our Motivations and problems that we want to solve. - 
          At Platy Studio, we combine our passion for high-quality cinema with cutting-edge AI technology to redefine video production. Inspired by the immense potential of great entertainment to uplift society and driven by our excitement about advancements in large language models, we are addressing challenges that resonate deeply with us consumers...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-12-06-our-motivation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-12-06-our-motivation/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decoding Voice Dubbing</title>
        <description>
          How Platy Studio&apos;s multi-dimentional Dubbing works - 
          In the world of dubbing, capturing the essence of the original speaker’s voice goes far beyond mere word-for-word translation. Our cutting-edge tech product focuses on several crucial aspects of speech to deliver a truly immersive and authentic dubbing experience. Let’s dive into the key elements that make our dubbing technology...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-12-06-Decoding-Voice-Dubbing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-12-06-Decoding-Voice-Dubbing/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample blog post to learn markdown tips</title>
        <description>
          There&apos;s lots to learn! - 
          This is a demo post to show you how to write blog posts with markdown. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/tables/etc.I also encourage you to look at the code that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-sample-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-sample-markdown/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
